[
    {
      "title": "1992 in Sport"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which NBA team won the 1992 NBA Finals?",
      "answer": "The Chicago Bulls"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which country hosted the 1992 Summer Olympics?",
      "answer": "Spain (in Barcelona)"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "In which French city were the 1992 Winter Olympics held?",
      "answer": "Albertville"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which tennis player won the Men’s Singles title at Wimbledon 1992?",
      "answer": "Andre Agassi"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which tennis player won the Women’s Singles title at Wimbledon 1992?",
      "answer": "Steffi Graf"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which country won the 1992 European Football Championship (Euro 92)?",
      "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which golfer won the 1992 Masters Tournament?",
      "answer": "Fred Couples"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which cricketer scored the most runs in the 1992 Cricket World Cup?",
      "answer": "Martin Crowe (New Zealand)"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which F1 driver won the 1992 Drivers’ Championship?",
      "answer": "Nigel Mansell"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Who was crowned the 1992 Ballon d’Or winner?",
      "answer": "Marco van Basten"
    }
  ]